{
  "array": [
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "The sun is?",
      "correct": "a star",
      "option1": "a planet",
      "option2": "a black-hole",
      "option3": "a quasar"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "The city of Nice is located in",
      "correct": "France",
      "option1": "Germany",
      "option2": "Italy",
      "option3": "Spain"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "The human beings lives on",
      "correct": "earth",
      "option1": "moon",
      "option2": "mars",
      "option3": "saturn"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "What is Python?",
      "correct": "programming language",
      "option1": "web app",
      "option2": "a printer",
      "option3": "a snake"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Who invented the telephone?",
      "correct": "Graham Bell",
      "option1": "Einstein",
      "option2": "Tesla",
      "option3": "Steve Jobs"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Which is more dense?",
      "correct": "water",
      "option1": "ice",
      "option2": "air",
      "option3": "helium"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Which continent is larger?",
      "correct": "Asia",
      "option1": "Africa",
      "option2": "Europe",
      "option3": "Oceania"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "The capital of Japan is?",
      "correct": "Tokio",
      "option1": "Yokohama",
      "option2": "Peking",
      "option3": "Nagasaki"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Most populated city in Colombia?",
      "correct": "Bogota",
      "option1": "Medellin",
      "option2": "Cali",
      "option3": "Cartagena"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Recommended hours of sleep",
      "correct": 8,
      "option1": 6,
      "option2": 12,
      "option3": 4
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Largest Planet on the solar system",
      "correct": "Jupiter",
      "option1": "Uranus",
      "option2": "Mercury",
      "option3": "Saturn"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Largest Animal on earth",
      "correct": "blue whale",
      "option1": "Shark",
      "option2": "Lion",
      "option3": "elephant"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Heaviest element in the periodic table",
      "correct": "Oganesson",
      "option1": "Radon",
      "option2": "Polonium",
      "option3": "Mercury"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Number of electrons on a Hydrogen Atom",
      "correct": 1,
      "option1": 2,
      "option2": 3,
      "option3": 4
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "In which country is located Taj mahal",
      "correct": "India",
      "option1": "China",
      "option2": "Taiwan",
      "option3": "Russia"
    },
    {
      "level": 4,
      "question": "What is the name of Poland in Polish?",
      "correct": "Polska",
      "option1": "Poland",
      "option2": "Polonnia",
      "option3": "Polask"
    },
    {
      "level": 4,
      "question": "Most used OS in the world?",
      "correct": "Windows",
      "option1": "Linux",
      "option2": "MacOS",
      "option3": "ChromeOS"
    },
    {
      "level": 4,
      "question": "how many stars have European union flag",
      "correct": 12,
      "option1": 10,
      "option2": 20,
      "option3": 18
    },
    {
      "level": 4,
      "question": "Which of the following languages is not object-oriented",
      "correct": "Haskell",
      "option1": "C++",
      "option2": "Java",
      "option3": "Python"
    },
    {
      "level": 4,
      "question": "What is the last letter of the Greek alphabet?",
      "correct": "omega",
      "option1": "delta",
      "option2": "nu",
      "option3": "phi"
    },
    {
      "level": 5,
      "question": "Chartreuse is a color between yellow and what?",
      "correct": "Green",
      "option1": "Blue",
      "option2": "Red",
      "option3": "Magenta"
    },
    {
      "level": 5,
      "question": "How many keys are there on a standard grand piano?",
      "correct": 88,
      "option1": 82,
      "option2": 92,
      "option3": 84
    },
    {
      "level": 5,
      "question": "What is faster than light",
      "correct": "Expansion of space-time",
      "option1": "photons",
      "option2": "nothing",
      "option3": "Singularity"
    },
    {
      "level": 5,
      "question": "What disease can be caused by a lack of Vitamin C?",
      "correct": "Scurvy",
      "option1": "diabetes",
      "option2": "Cirrhosis",
      "option3": "anemia"
    },
    {
      "level": 5,
      "question": "What did Temujin change his name to?",
      "correct": "Genghis Khan",
      "option1": "Kublai Kahn",
      "option2": "Lenin",
      "option3": "Napoleon"
    }
  ]
}